<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on C. Seth Lester, ASA</title>
    <link>https://cslester.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on C. Seth Lester, ASA</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; Copyright 2020, C. S. Lester</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cslester.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Rise and Fall of Sourdough</title>
      <link>https://cslester.com/posts/sourdough/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cslester.com/posts/sourdough/</guid>
      <description>The Rise and Fall of Sourdough Over the course of our new shelter-in-place lives in the first half of 2020, I was curious about how to best tell the story of America’s new fascination with sourdough - and whether or not that fascination has persisted through the year and into the summer.
The following code is a demonstration of how to web scrape Google trends for location-specific search trends and organize this information visually in the form of an animated choropleth (heat map) that shows change over time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Actuarial Standards of Practice: A brief visual analysis</title>
      <link>https://cslester.com/posts/asop-viz/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cslester.com/posts/asop-viz/</guid>
      <description>This content was generated using a R Markdown Notebook. The code / .RMD file used to build this page, as well as additional documentation and resources, are all located on my personal GitHub page. A slightly revised version of this content was posted on LinkedIn.
What do actuaries do? I volunteered (with some eagerness) to teach the R training sessions to the bright and talented “virtual” actuarial intern cohorts we have at Cigna this year in our Philadelphia office, and I wanted to kick off the presentation with a showcase of the flexibility and power that the R language and RStudio IDE can bring to a project, all while providing my spin on the so-called million-dollar question: “What do actuaries do?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Embracing a New Dimension of Model Tuning in Actuarial Model Development</title>
      <link>https://cslester.com/posts/quantified-fairness/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cslester.com/posts/quantified-fairness/</guid>
      <description>Late last autumn, I took an opportunity to respond to the Society of Actuaries&#39; call for essays about potential disruptions and innovations in the actuarial practice space.
The bad news: I didn&amp;rsquo;t win one of the top prizes.
The good news: My essay was published anyways, and you can read it here.
Most of the essay serves as a rehash and survey of work explained in The Ethical Algorithm: The Science of Socially Aware Algorithm Design, but ends with some discussion about how the evolving generation of new actuarial modeling and predictive analytics has considerations yet to be worked out by the Actuarial Standards Board as they prepare to release the new, long-awaited Modeling ASOP.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
