<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>C. Seth Lester, ASA</title>
    <link>https://cslester.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on C. Seth Lester, ASA</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; Copyright 2020, C. S. Lester</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://cslester.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Visual Résumé</title>
      <link>https://cslester.com/resume/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cslester.com/resume/resume/</guid>
      <description>The code used to build this visual résumé was was created in R Markdown and is available at my Github site. If you would prefer a more traditional résumé (typeset in LaTeX), then I have that in Adobe PDF format as well.
Work Experience Education and Professional Designations Technical Competencies References </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Actuarial Standards of Practice: A brief visual analysis</title>
      <link>https://cslester.com/posts/asop-viz/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cslester.com/posts/asop-viz/</guid>
      <description>This content was generated using a R Markdown Notebook. The code / .RMD file used to build this page, as well as additional documentation and resources, are all located on my personal GitHub page. A slightly revised version of this content was posted on LinkedIn.
What do actuaries do? I volunteered (with some eagerness) to teach the R training sessions to the bright and talented “virtual” actuarial intern cohorts we have at Cigna this year in our Philadelphia office, and I wanted to kick off the presentation with a showcase of the flexibility and power that the R language and RStudio IDE can bring to a project, all while providing my spin on the so-called million-dollar question: “What do actuaries do?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>